Help!
Are we supposed to go to the Control Room?
No way.
They're calling for help.
I think we should go save them.
Let's rescue them.
Let's go.
Am I bringing my mascot out with me?
Ah!
That scared me!
Sis!
Is that an NPC?
Is he going to interact with me?
Why is the NPC stuck?
There's key evidence here!
"Key evidence must never be discovered." EP 09...
I saw your gun.
What's going on?
Why are the NPCs and cameramen all frozen?
Time is rewinding!
Right?
That last one ended up right here...
Does this zombie have clues on him?
Here, here, here, here, here!
Is he...
It's an arrow!
Whoa!
Okay, okay.
It really is the Control Room.
It really is!
So you guys were right here.
You're the ones who set the AC to five degrees!
This isn't the AC room.
You weren't the ones controlling the AC.
Why is someone tracking our faces?
And...
I'm still on a fixed camera.
This is my PD!
What does that mean?
Hey!
Hold on a sec.
What-what-what is this thing?
Look, what does "don't press together" mean?
I'm gonna press it anyway!
"Don't press together."
Then let's press them together!
Come on. One...
Two, three!
Whoa, whoa!
Great job, everyone!
You startled me.
Happy wrap!
This is their daily script, Succession War First Draft: How to Hide Key Evidence.
The best way is to hide it.
Hide it somewhere.
As long as no one can find it.
Come here, come here.
Not in the same spot.
It gets easier the second time.
You can hide it in wall cracks.
Or under the bed.
Okay, okay.
I got it.
I'm taking this one with me.
I'll study it carefully.
Alright.
Great job.
Great job, great job.
Thanks, everyone.
Happy wrap!
Thank you.
Ah.
Good job.
Thank you.